to autumn by John Keats season of mists
and mellow fruitfulness close bosom
friend of the maturing Sun conspiring
with him how to load and bless with
fruit the vines that round the thatch
eaves run to bend with apples the mosque
cottage trees and fill all fruit with
ripeness to the core to swell the gourd
and plump the hazel shells with a sweet
kernel to set budding more and still
more later flowers for the bees until
they think warm days will never cease
for summer has or brimmed their clammy
cells who hath not seen the off to
midthigh store sometimes whoever seeks
abroad may find the sitting careless on
a granary floor thy hair soft lifted by
the winnowing wind arana half reaped
furrow sound asleep drowsed with a few
muck spares the next swath and all its
twined flowers and sometimes like a
Gleaner thou dust keep steady thy laden
head across a brook or by a cider press
with patient look thou watches the last
usings hours by hours what are the songs
of spring I where are they think not of
them thou hast thy music too while bard
clouds bloom the soft dying day and
touched the stubble plains with rosy hue
then an away awful choir the small NAT
sworn among the river sallows borne
aloft or sinking as the light wind lives
or dies and full-grown lambs loud bleep
from hilly born hedge crickets sing and
now with the treble soft the red breast
whistles from a garden croft and
gathering swallows Twitter in the skies
and a poem